{
    "subject": "Charles_VII_of_France",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Marie_of_Anjou",
    "human_readable": "Charles VII of France is married to Marie of Anjou.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9884187579154968,
            "question": "Is Marie of Anjou the wife of Charles VII of France?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9778776168823242,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the marriage of Charles VII of France and Marie of Anjou?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9376027584075928,
            "question": "Which French monarch was married to Marie of Anjou?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9346458315849304,
            "question": "Was Charles VII of France in a union with Marie of Anjou?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9190340042114258,
            "question": "Who is Charles VII of France married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8665846586227417,
            "question": "Who was Marie of Anjou married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8375339508056641,
            "question": "To whom was Charles VII of France wed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7524046301841736,
            "question": "What is the name of Charles VII of France's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7284007668495178,
            "question": "What is the name of Charles VII of France's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49820011854171753,
            "question": "Who was the queen consort of Charles VII of France?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Charles VII of France is married to Marie of Anjou.",
            "html": "yago_21778_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Charles VII of France's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_21778_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Charles VII of France's wife?",
            "html": "yago_21778_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To whom was Charles VII of France wed?",
            "html": "yago_21778_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21778_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21778_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21778_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21778_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21778_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21778_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21778_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21778_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21778_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21778_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n* Document 1 (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_21778/re-ranker-msmarco/7.txt) mentions \"Marie d'Anjou, Queen of France (1404-1463), was the wife of Charles VII.\"\n* Document 2 (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_21778/re-ranker-msmarco/43.txt) mentions \"Marie's family began funding Charles and his military\" but does not explicitly state that Marie is the wife of Charles VII.\n* Document 3 (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_21778/re-ranker-msmarco/7.txt) again mentions \"Marie d'Anjou, Queen of France, was the wife of Charles VII.\"\n* Documents 4 and 5 (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_21778/re-ranker-msmarco/72.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_21778/re-ranker-msmarco/66.txt) mention \"Marie of Anjou, Marie d\u2019Anjou, 1404-1463, Queen of France as the wife of King Charles VII\" which supports the triple.\n* Document 6 (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_21778/re-ranker-msmarco/33.txt) mentions \"Marie of Anjou, wife of King Charles VII of France\" which further supports the triple.\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Charles VII of France is married to Marie of Anjou.\n\nTherefore, the response is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Charles VII of France is married to Marie of Anjou.\" Both files mention that Marie d'Anjou or Marie of Anjou was the wife of Charles VII of France."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}